Wauregan and Quinebaug Company Records 1981.0010
Archives and Special Collections at the Thomas J. Dodd Research Center, University of Connecticut Library
- Series VI: Labor Records, 1855-1958
  - Subseries C: Personnel Files, 1936-1958
    - Schimmelpfennig, Albert H., Jr., 1951 (Box 226:4508)
    - Schimmelpfennig, Albert H., Sr., 1956 (Box 226:4509)
    - Schimmelpfennig, Laura E. D., 1952 (Box 226:4510)
    - Schimmelpfennig, Otto A., 1941 (Box 226:4511)
    - Schoffield, Flora A., 1941 (Box 226:4512)
    - Schroth, Arthur L., 1938 (Box 226:4513)
    - Schroth, Edith, 1948 (Box 226:4514)
    - Schroth, Lillian, 1955 (Box 226:4515)
    - Schroth, Rita B. Lesage, 1946 (Box 226:4516)
    - Schroth, Norman E., 1957 (Box 226:4517)
    - SChroth, Rudolph R., 1953 (Box 226:4518)
    - Schwartz, Sadelle, 1948 (Box 226:4519)
    - Scott, David, 1939 (Box 226:4520)
    - Scott, Everett R., 1946 (Box 226:4521)
    - Scott, Harry W., 1944 (Box 226:4522)
    - Scott, Janet R., 1943 (Box 226:4523)
    - Scott, Joseph, 1947 (Box 226:4524)
    - Scott, Victorine R., 1947 (Box 226:4525)
    - Sears, Della, 1957 (Box 226:4526)
    - Seddon, Harriet A., 1937 (Box 226:4527)
    - Seguin, Eugene J., 1937 (Box 226:4528)
    - Seguin, Marie A. V., 1951 (Box 226:4529)
    - Seguin, Raymond J., 1951 (Box 226:4530)
    - Senecal, Alphonse, 1954 (Box 226:4531)
    - Senecal, Arthur, 1940 (Box 226:4532)
    - Senecal, Edmond, 1940 (Box 226:4533)
    - Senecal, Henry J., 1956 (Box 226:4534)
    - Senecal, Herbert J., 1946 (Box 226:4535)
    - Senecal, Isabel D., 1948 (Box 226:4536)
    - Senecal, Jean E., 1956 (Box 226:4537)
    - Senecal, Peter J., 1944 (Box 226:4538)
    - Senecal, Regina, 1948 (Box 226:4539)
    - Senecal, Rose B. G., 1937 (Box 226:4540)
    - Seney, Raphael, 1937 (Box 226:4541)
    - Sevigny, George, 1954 (Box 226:4542)
    - Sewart, Norman, 1950 (Box 226:4543)
    - Shaw, Bertha D. V., 1950 (Box 226:4544)
    - Shaw, Florence Carpenter, 1956 (Box 226:4545)
    - Shaw, Nadine, 1942 (Box 226:4546)
    - Shaw, Oscar, 1948 (Box 226:4547)
    - Shaw, Ronald, 1942 (Box 226:4548)
    - Shaw, Thomas, 1954 (Box 226:4549)
    - Shawchuk, Mike, 1937 (Box 226:4550)
    - Shawchuk, Rose H., 1940 (Box 226:4551)
    - Shifflet, Ida L. Charron, 1954 (Box 226:4552)
    - Shikrallah, June M., 1945 (Box 226:4553)
    - Shimski, Mary K., 1937 (Box 226:4554)
    - Shippee, Dora R., 1954 (Box 226:4555)
    - Shippee, Claude, 1946 (Box 226:4556)
    - Shippee, Eugene P., 1938 (Box 226:4557)
    - Shippee, Octavia B., 1940 (Box 226:4558)
    - Shippee, Ralph, 1951 (Box 226:4559)
    - Shippee, Walter A., 1951 (Box 226:4560)
    - Shola, John A., 1939 (Box 226:4561)
    - Siembab, Agnes P., 1939 (Box 226:4562)
    - Siembab, Anthony W., 1941 (Box 226:4563)
    - Silva, Anthony F., 1938 (Box 226:4564)
    - Silva, Emmanuel J., 1937 (Box 226:4565)
    - Silva, Louis, 1949 (Box 226:4566)
    - Silva, Manuel, 1938 (Box 226:4567)
    - Silva, Richard, 1956 (Box 226:4568)
    - Simmons, Foster D., 1956 (Box 226:4569)
    - Simmons, James C., 1953 (Box 226:4570)
    - Simonds, Albert F., 1937 (Box 226:4571)
    - Simonds, Hilda, 1948 (Box 226:4572)
    - Simonds, Patricia Barre, 1948 (Box 226:4573)
    - Simonds, Walter F., 1939 (Box 226:4574)
    - Simoneau, Antoinette, 1942 (Box 226:4575)
    - Simoneau, Armand L., 1937 (Box 226:4576)
    - Simoneau, Minnie G., 1941 (Box 226:4577)
    - Simoneau, Rose B., 1941 (Box 226:4578)
    - Sinkewicz, Olga, 1939 (Box 226:4579)
    - Sinkewicz, William, 1949 (Box 226:4580)
    - Sinkoski, Josephine L. K., 1945 (Box 226:4581)
    - Sipila, George, 1945 (Box 226:4582)
    - Sivley, Lucille Lacharite, 1955 (Box 226:4583)
    - Skinner, Bernice, 1953 (Box 226:4584)
    - Skinner, Bert L., 1941 (Box 226:4585)
    - Skirvin, Doris, 1953 (Box 226:4586)
    - Skorupski, Helen, 1940 (Box 226:4587)
    - Sliva, Helen, 1956 (Box 226:4588)
    - Sliva, John, 1952 (Box 226:4589)
    - Sliva, Joseph J., 1942 (Box 226:4590)
    - Sliva, Sophie K., 1939 (Box 226:4591)
    - Smalley, David, 1946 (Box 226:4592)
    - Smith, Anne, 1953 (Box 226:4593)
    - Smith, Albert W., 1940 (Box 226:4594)
    - Smith, Alfred A., 1941 (Box 226:4595)
    - Smith, Blanche L. P., 1942 (Box 226:4596)
    - Smith, Clarinda V., 1953 (Box 226:4597)
    - Smith, Doris Masse, 1948 (Box 226:4598)
    - Smith, Earle W., 1941 (Box 226:4599)
    - Smith, Fabiola, 1950 (Box 226:4600)
    - Smith, Frederick K., 1952 (Box 226:4601)
    - Smith, George, 1947 (Box 226:4602)
    - Smith, Hilliard H., Jr., 1938 (Box 226:4603)
    - Smith, Lillie, 1952 (Box 226:4604)
    - Smith, Lillian, 1946 (Box 226:4605)
    - Smith, Ralph E., 1939 (Box 226:4606)
    - Smith, Rita Brodeur, 1946 (Box 226:4607)
    - Smith, Robert, 1946 (Box 226:4608)
    - Smith, Romuald L., 1940 (Box 226:4609)
    - Smith, Stanley J., 1952 (Box 226:4610)
    - Smith, Victor, 1955 (Box 226:4611)
    - Smith, Victor, 1955 (Box 226:4612)
    - Smith, Wilfred A., 1950 (Box 226:4613)
    - Smura, Blanche, 1943 (Box 226:4614)
    - Snurkowski, Rita J. Corby, 1947 (Box 226:4615)
    - Soares, Abel, 1941 (Box 226:4616)
    - Soares, John, 1941 (Box 226:4617)
    - Socquet, George J., 1951 (Box 226:4618)
    - Soderman, John W., 1952 (Box 226:4619)
    - Solomon, Hassen, 1955 (Box 226:4620)
    - Solomon, Alexandra Costa (Solomos), 1949 (Box 226:4621)
    - Solomos, Kosties, 1950 (Box 226:4622)
    - Sooar, Valdemar, 1951 (Box 226:4623)
    - Sopkiw, Dmytro, 1939 (Box 226:4624)
    - Sopkiw, Mary C., 1941 (Box 226:4625)
    - Sopkiw, Peter, 1942 (Box 226:4626)
    - Sopkiw, Walter, 1942 (Box 226:4627)
    - Sorel, Clarence, 1956 (Box 226:4628)
    - Soucy, Eugene C., 1939 (Box 226:4629)
    - Soucy, Paul Isador, Sr., 1943 (Box 226:4630)
    - Soucy, Paul J., 1941 (Box 226:4631)
    - Soule, Howard A., 1952 (Box 226:4632)
    - Sowerbutts, John, 1941 (Box 226:4633)
    - Spau, Mary C., 1942 (Box 227:4634)
    - Spaulding, Lucille, 1953 (Box 227:4635)
    - Spaulding, Roberta, 1946 (Box 227:4636)
    - Spencer, John M., 1937 (Box 227:4637)
    - Spink, Fred E., 1951 (Box 227:4638)
    - Spinoso, John, 1951 (Box 227:4639)
    - Sposato, Elsie M., 1953 (Box 227:4640)
    - Squillacote, Blanche C., 1944 (Box 227:4641)
    - Squire, Arthur, 1942 (Box 227:4642)
    - Sroka, Sophie S., 1941 (Box 227:4643)
    - Stachura, Sophie M., 1943 (Box 227:4644)
    - Stachura, Stefanie S., 1943 (Box 227:4645)
    - Stahecki, Peter J., 1938 (Box 227:4646)
    - Stahecki, Rose Anna M. Bouchard, 1950 (Box 227:4647)
    - Stankovich, John, 1948 (Box 227:4648)
    - Stanley, Elsie E. C., 1937 (Box 227:4649)
    - Starkweather, Barbara, 1945 (Box 227:4650)
    - Staskiewicz, Adam, 1939 (Box 227:4651)
    - Staskiewicz, Chester J., 1938 (Box 227:4652)
    - Staskiewiecz, Sophie, 1939 (Box 227:4653)
    - Staskivtch, Agnes, 1949 (Box 227:4654)
    - Staskivtch, Edward (Staskiwiez), 1942 (Box 227:4655)
    - Staskivtch, Eva K. (Staskiewicz), 1943 (Box 227:4656)
    - Stakivtch, Joseph A., 1956 (Box 227:4657)
    - Staskivtch, Peter (Staskiewicz), 1943 (Box 227:4658)
    - Stawasz, Peter F., 1939 (Box 227:4659)
    - Stedman, Helen, 1952 (Box 227:4660)
    - Stedman, Philip, 1951 (Box 227:4661)
    - Steele, George G., 1945 (Box 227:4662)
    - Steele, Henry I., 1946 (Box 227:4663)
    - Steen, Irene Masse, 1941 (Box 227:4664)
    - Steinbacher, Joseph, 1952 (Box 227:4665)
    - Steinman, George, 1943 (Box 227:4666)
    - Stewart, Guilford, 1951 (Box 227:4667)
    - Stillwell, James, 1946 (Box 227:4668)
    - Stoddert, Norman, 1942 (Box 227:4669)
    - Stone, Claude, 1955 (Box 227:4670)
    - Stott, Florence, 1953 (Box 227:4671)
    - Stones, James Stanley, 1950 (Box 227:4672)
    - Streich, Arthur, 1956 (Box 227:4673)
    - Streich, Cecelia L., 1942 (Box 227:4674)
    - Streyczek, John F., 1937 (Box 227:4675)
    - Streich, Robert, 1956 (Box 227:4676)
    - Streyczek, Stanley, 1937 (Box 227:4677)
    - Stryczek, Sophie S., 1953 (Box 227:4678)
    - Strzempek, Frank, 1943 (Box 227:4679)
    - Strzesak, Stanley, 1938 (Box 227:4680)
    - Stuyniski, George, 1952 (Box 227:4681)
    - Stuyniski, Walter H., 1950 (Box 227:4682)
    - Sudol, Mary V., 1954 (Box 227:4683)
    - Sugalski, Adam, 1947 (Box 227:4684)
    - Sugalski, Edmond Joseph, 1941 (Box 227:4685)
    - Sugalski, Lionel J., 1941 (Box 227:4686)
    - Sullivan, Arthur, 1940 (Box 227:4687)
    - Sullivan, John H., 1952 (Box 227:4688)
    - Sullivan, John L., 1950 (Box 227:4689)
    - Sullivan, John L., 1939 (Box 227:4690)
    - Sullivan, Lucy, 1953 (Box 227:4691)
    - Sullivan, Lillian, 1956 (Box 227:4692)
    - Suominen, Kalle W., 1953 (Box 227:4693)
    - Supka, Sophie B., 1944 (Box 227:4694)
    - Surprenant, Annette D., 1940 (Box 227:4695)
    - Surprenant, Florence B., 1940 (Box 227:4696)
    - Surprenant, Lucille Tetreault, 1956 (Box 227:4697)
    - Surprenant, Oscar E., 1937 (Box 227:4698)
    - Surprenant, Robert, 1956 (Box 227:4699)
    - Surprenant, Roland E., 1955 (Box 227:4700)
    - Surprenant, Rudolphe, 1950 (Box 227:4701)
    - Surprenant, Rudolphe, Jr., 1950 (Box 227:4702)
    - Sutton, Harry, 1951 (Box 227:4703)
    - Sutton, Stephen, Jr., 1942 (Box 227:4704)
    - Suzik, Alexander, 1947 (Box 227:4705)
    - Suzik, Theresa, 1953 (Box 227:4706)
    - Swan, Bertha Aubin, 1952 (Box 227:4707)
    - Swank, John, 1953 (Box 227:4708)
    - Swanson, Josephine A., 1954 (Box 227:4709)
    - Swanson, David, 1956 (Box 227:4710)
    - Swantek, Joseph P., 1937 (Box 227:4711)
    - Swantek, Theresa W., 1937 (Box 227:4712)
    - Sweet, Albert K., 1947 (Box 227:4713)
    - Sweet, Elton Stuart, 1950 (Box 227:4714)
    - Sweet, Rose Belanger, 1955 (Box 227:4716)
    - Sylvester, Alcide J., 1956 (Box 227:4717)
    - Sylvestre, Henry A., 1948 (Box 227:4718)
    - Sypek, John E., 1937 (Box 227:4719)
    - Sypek, Louis E., 1941 (Box 227:4720)
    - Sypek, Martin F., 1937 (Box 227:4721)
    - Szela, John Joseph, 1943 (Box 227:4722)
    - Szela, Sophie C., 1950 (Box 227:4723)
    - Szela, Theodore J., 1937 (Box 227:4724)
    - Szeredy, Barbara LaChance, 1954 (Box 227:4725)
    - Szeredy, William J., 1957 (Box 227:4726)
    - Szeredy, William, Jr., 1956 (Box 227:4727)
    - Szeredy, Pearl, 1957 (Box 227:4728)
    - Szewcyk, John, 1943 (Box 227:4729)
    - Szewcyk, Louise Z., 1950 (Box 227:4730)
    - Szymurski, Adam S., 1939 (Box 227:4731)
    - Tabbis, Anna G., 1952 (Box 227:4732)
    - Tahk, Pauline, 1954 (Box 227:4733)
    - Talva, Haerdi, 1953 (Box 227:4734)
    - Tampas, Georgia D., 1937 (Box 227:4735)
    - Tampas, Louis S., 1941 (Box 227:4736)
    - Tancred, Arthur, 1948 (Box 227:4737)
    - Tanguay, Anselme, 1950 (Box 227:4738)
    - Tanguay, Gerard L., 1942 (Box 227:4739)
    - Tanguay, Rose, 1942 (Box 227:4740)
    - Tanner, Doris, 1955 (Box 227:4741)
    - Tanner, Warren (Dr.), 1954 (Box 227:4742)
    - Tarbox, Irene A., 1955 (Box 227:4743)
    - Tarbox, Ralph Herbert, 1956 (Box 227:4744)
    - Tarrell, Yvonne D., 1940 (Box 227:4745)
    - Taschereau, Laura, 1950 (Box 227:4746)
    - Tavernier, Alfred, 1949 (Box 227:4747)
    - Tavernier, Theresa, 1952 (Box 227:4748)
    - Taylor, Raymond, 1956 (Box 227:4749)
    - Tefft, William, 1956 (Box 227:4750)
    - Tegtmeier, Ernest, 1952 (Box 227:4751)
    - Terreault, David, 1944 (Box 227:4752)
    - Tervonen, John, 1953 (Box 227:4753)
    - Terwilliger, Maurice, 1946 (Box 227:4754)
    - Tessier, Conrad, 1939 (Box 227:4755)
    - Tessier, Laurent C., 1940 (Box 227:4756)
    - Tessier, Rita, 1955 (Box 227:4757)
    - Tessier, William, 1951 (Box 227:4758)
    - Tetreault, Albert H., 1953 (Box 227:4759)
    - Tetreault, Angeline, 1939 (Box 227:4760)
    - Tetreault, Anna, 1944 (Box 227:4761)
    - Tetreault, Archie, 1938 (Box 227:4762)
    - Tetreault, Arthur P., 1938 (Box 227:4763)
    - Tetreault, Doris, 1946 (Box 227:4764)
    - Tetreault, Dorothy Benoit, 1942 (Box 227:4765)
    - Tetreault, Edith, 1938 (Box 227:4766)
    - Tetreault, Ella, 1950 (Box 227:4767)
    - Tetreault, Ernest, 1938 (Box 227:4768)
    - Tetreault, Estelle M., 1938 (Box 227:4769)
    - Tetreault, Frank, 1953 (Box 227:4770)
    - Tetreault, Janet, 1941 (Box 227:4771)
    - Tetreault, Jeannette M., 1937 (Box 227:4773)
    - Tetreault, Joseph E., 1939 (Box 227:4774)
    - Tetreault, Juliette T., 1938 (Box 227:4775)
    - Tetreault, Lillian O., 1938 (Box 227:4776)
    - Tetreault, Loranda H., 1953 (Box 227:4777)
    - Tetreault, Louis, 1938 (Box 227:4778)
    - Tetreault, Ludivine, 1956 (Box 227:4779)
    - Tetreault, Norman, 1955 (Box 227:4780)
    - Tetreault, Philias D., 1937 (Box 227:4781)
    - Tetreault, Rosario, 1953 (Box 227:4782)
    - Tetreault, Rose A., 1941 (Box 227:4783)
    - Tetreault, Theodore, 1943 (Box 227:4784)
    - Tetreault, Theodore A., 1937 (Box 227:4785)
    - Tetreault, Yvonne M., 1937 (Box 227:4786)
    - Theriaque, Clarence, 1955 (Box 227:4787)
    - Theriaque, Dora M., 1955 (Box 227:4788)
    - Theriaque, Dora O., 1944 (Box 227:4789)
    - Theriaque, Eugene, 1955 (Box 227:4790)
    - Theriaque, Joseph H., 1954 (Box 227:4791)
    - Theriaque, Mabel, 1955 (Box 227:4792)
    - Theriaque, Ovila J., 1940 (Box 227:4793)
    - Theriaque, Robert E., 1955 (Box 227:4794)
    - Theriaque, Roland J., 1952 (Box 227:4795)
    - Theriault, Leroy E., 1946 (Box 227:4796)
    - Therrien, Arthur, 1955 (Box 227:4797)
    - Therrien, Armande, 1954 (Box 227:4798)
    - Theroux, Adrienne, 1948 (Box 227:4799)
    - Theroux, Alfred H., Sr., 1937 (Box 227:4800)
    - Theroux, Cecilia B., 1937 (Box 227:4801)
    - Theroux, Exilda, 1945 (Box 227:4802)
    - Theroux, Laurent, 1948 (Box 227:4803)
    - Theroux, Raymond, 1957 (Box 227:4804)
    - Thevirge, Cordelia L., 1937 (Box 227:4805)
    - Thevirge, George, 1949 (Box 227:4806)
    - Thibeault, Aime E., 1952 (Box 227:4807)
    - Thibeault, Alfred, 1942 (Box 227:4808)
    - Thibeault, Bertha, 1956 (Box 227:4811)
    - Thibeault, Eva D., 1939 (Box 227:4809)
    - Thibeault, Conrad J., 1956 (Box 227:4810)
    - Thibeault, George, 1944 (Box 227:4812)
    - Thibeault, Helen C., 1941 (Box 227:4813)
    - Thibeault, Jean Marie, 1953 (Box 227:4814)
    - Thibeault, Laurent J., 1947 (Box 227:4815)
    - Thibeault, Louis, 1947 (Box 227:4816)
    - Thibeault, Lucien, 1937 (Box 227:4817)
    - Thibeault, Virginia C., 1941 (Box 227:4818)
    - Thibeault, William Leon, 1941 (Box 227:4819)
    - Thibeodeau, Moise, 1946 (Box 227:4820)
    - Thomas, Antoinette, 1949 (Box 227:4821)
    - Thomas, Claire Mae R., 1939 (Box 227:4822)
    - Thomas, Joseph W., 1949 (Box 227:4823)
    - Thomas, Joseph, 1941 (Box 227:4824)
    - Thomas, Julia, 1944 (Box 227:4825)
    - Thomas, Lianna G., 1950 (Box 227:4826)
    - Thompson, Ernest, 1952 (Box 227:4827)
    - Thompson, Everett, 1956 (Box 227:4828)
    - Thompson, Harriet, 1947 (Box 227:4829)
    - Thompson, Henry, Jr., 1946 (Box 227:4830)
    - Thompson, Henry, Sr., 1943 (Box 227:4831)
    - Thornley, Angela, 1942 (Box 227:4832)
    - Thornton, June Moran, 1947 (Box 227:4833)
    - Thuotte, Eva C., 1953 (Box 227:4834)
    - Thuotte, Joseph A., 1947 (Box 227:4835)
    - Thurlow, Harry C., 1949 (Box 227:4836)
    - Tobin, Helen G., 1951 (Box 227:4837)
    - Todd, Arthur, 1956 (Box 227:4838)
    - Topping, Henry, 1954 (Box 227:4839)
    - Tomasik, Mary, 1956 (Box 227:4840)
    - Tomasik, Rudolph, 1957 (Box 227:4841)
    - Touchette, Ida C., 1939 (Box 227:4842)
    - Touchette, Leon, 1956 (Box 227:4843)
    - Tourtellotte, Alma, 1947 (Box 227:4844)
    - Tourtellotte, Carolus N., 1942 (Box 227:4845)
    - Tourtellotte, Ernestine, 1943 (Box 227:4846)
    - Tourtellotte, Irving, 1956 (Box 227:4847)
    - Townsend, Lillian Daley, 1956 (Box 227:4848)
    - Tracy, Annie W., 1938 (Box 228:4849)
    - Tracy, Dorothy M., 1944 (Box 228:4850)
    - Tracy, Harvey B., Jr., 1944 (Box 228:4851)
    - Trahan, Albert E., 1952 (Box 228:4852)
    - Trahan, Edeace J., 1940 (Box 228:4853)
    - Trahan, Eliodore, 1950 (Box 228:4854)
    - Trahan, Florida M., 1942 (Box 228:4855)
    - Trahan, Henry L., 1950 (Box 228:4856)
    - Trahan, Lionel J., 1949 (Box 228:4857)
    - Trahan, Rachel Irene, 1948 (Box 228:4858)
    - Trahan, Rose F. B., 1942 (Box 228:4859)
    - Trahan, Rudolph, 1954 (Box 228:4860)
    - Trahan, Theodore, 1941 (Box 228:4861)
    - Tremblay, Anna, 1956 (Box 228:4862)
    - Tremblay, Armand Joseph, 1940 (Box 228:4863)
    - Tremblay, Elizabeth, 1955 (Box 228:4864)
    - Trembly, Norman, 1956 (Box 228:4865)
    - Tripp, Leslie Calvin, 1941 (Box 228:4866)
    - Trudeau, Harvey J., 1939 (Box 228:4867)
    - Tsakonas, Basil T., 1952 (Box 228:4868)
    - Tsakonas, George T., 1942 (Box 228:4869)
    - Tsotsones, Nicholas, 1941 (Box 228:4870)
    - Tsotsones, Peter D., 1940 (Box 228:4871)
    - Tucker, Marie Jeanne, 1952 (Box 228:4872)
    - Tucker, George, Jr., 1942 (Box 228:4873)
    - Tumicki, Jeanette, 1952 (Box 228:4874)
    - Turcotte, Eva, 1956 (Box 228:4875)
    - Turcotte, Henedine V., 1939 (Box 228:4876)
    - Turcotte, Joseph, 1942 (Box 228:4877)
    - Turcotte, Marie M. L., 1952 (Box 228:4878)
    - Turenne, Rose L., 1941 (Box 228:4879)
    - Turgeon, Albert, 1957 (Box 228:4880)
    - Turney, Dora M. J., 1953 (Box 228:4881)
    - Turney, Elmer C., 1937 (Box 228:4882)
    - Turrney, Byron M., 1939 (Box 228:4883)
    - Tyler, Robert, 1956 (Box 228:4884)
    - Ulman, Frances, 1942 (Box 228:4885)
    - Ulman, John, 1942 (Box 228:4886)
    - Uerales, Herkles E., 1950 (Box 228:4887)
    - Urgell, George, 1955 (Box 228:4888)
    - Utz, Alfred D., 1943 (Box 228:4889)
    - Utz, Louis August, 1943 (Box 228:4890)
    - Vachon, Edmond, 1937 (Box 228:4891)
    - Valen, Charles S., 1942 (Box 228:4892)
    - Valancourt, Arthur B., 1945 (Box 228:4893)
    - Valliere, Lucille T., 1937 (Box 228:4894)
    - Vanasse, Adelard, 1951 (Box 228:4895)
    - Vanasse, Germaine M. O. D., 1939 (Box 228:4896)
    - Vanasse, Grace, 1952 (Box 228:4897)
    - Vanasse, Harry, 1952 (Box 228:4898)
    - Vandal, Frank J., 1954 (Box 228:4899)
    - Vandale, Edward, Jr., 1955 (Box 228:4900)
    - Vandale, Mary Jane, 1950 (Box 228:4901)
    - Vandall, Rachel, 1952 (Box 228:4902)
    - Vandale, Salvadore V., 1941 (Box 228:4903)
    - Vandale, Wilfred, 1956 (Box 228:4904)
    - Vandall, Alcidas, 1941 (Box 228:4905)
    - Vargas, Manuel J., 1951 (Box 228:4906)
    - Vargas, Margaret, 1951 (Box 228:4907)
    - Varieur, Agnes B., 1941 (Box 228:4908)
    - Varieur, Alfred, 1939 (Box 228:4909)
    - Varieur, Angela G., 1939 (Box 228:4910)
    - Varieur, Annette Rose, 1942 (Box 228:4911)
    - Varieur, Hormidas, 1953 (Box 228:4912)
    - Varieur, Joseph T., 1945 (Box 228:4913)
    - Vashon, Emil, 1957 (Box 228:4914)
    - Vaurala, Uno Olovi, 1956 (Box 228:4915)
    - Vaz, Bermina, 1956 (Box 228:4916)
    - Veer, Marie, 1955 (Box 228:4917)
    - Veilleux, Alcide, 1956 (Box 228:4918)
    - Veilleux, Evelyn, 1951 (Box 228:4919)
    - Veilleux, Irene M., 1937 (Box 228:4920)
    - Vermette, Alfred, 1937 (Box 228:4921)
    - Vermette, Isidore A., 1937 (Box 228:4922)
    - Verraneault, Alfred, 1948 (Box 228:4923)
    - Verraneault, Andrew Edward, 1942 (Box 228:4924)
    - Verraneault, Anna, 1942 (Box 228:4925)
    - Verraneault, Diana S., 1956 (Box 228:4926)
    - Verraneault, Eldora, 1957 (Box 228:4927)
    - Verraneault, Emma Chatelle, 1952 (Box 228:4928)
    - Verraneault, Henry, 1956 (Box 228:4929)
    - Verraneault, Lionel, 1952 (Box 228:4930)
    - Verraneault, Medora, 1947 (Box 228:4931)
    - Verraneault, Raymond, 1953 (Box 228:4932)
    - Verraneault, Walter, 1953 (Box 228:4933)
    - Verrier, Anna Mary, 1951 (Box 228:4934)
    - Verrieur, Marcella, 1955 (Box 228:4935)
    - Vertefeuille, Irene, 1953 (Box 228:4936)
    - Vevia, Anna L., 1954 (Box 228:4937)
    - Vezina, Gerard, 1952 (Box 228:4938)
    - Vezina, Henedine F., 1942 (Box 228:4939)
    - Vezina, Rose, 1957 (Box 228:4940)
    - Vickers, John W., 1951 (Box 228:4941)
    - Vickers, Marie J., 1953 (Box 228:4942)
    - Vien, Arthur, 1944 (Box 228:4943)
    - Viens, Arthur J., 1955 (Box 228:4944)
    - Viens, Bella M., 1945 (Box 228:4945)
    - Viens, Eva, 1939 (Box 228:4946)
    - Viens, Ovila J., 1937 (Box 228:4947)
    - Vincent, Alice G., 1938 (Box 228:4948)
    - Vincent, Alphema S., 1937 (Box 228:4949)
    - Vincent, Cecile A., 1942 (Box 228:4950)
    - Vincent, Elsie J., 1942 (Box 228:4951)
    - Vincent, Ernest W., 1939 (Box 228:4952)
    - Vincent, George P., 1939 (Box 228:4953)
    - Vincent, Helen Olivina, 1942 (Box 228:4954)
    - Vincent, Jeannette, 1956 (Box 228:4955)
    - Vincent, Laura, 1948 (Box 228:4956)
    - Vincent, Lawrence N., 1939 (Box 228:4957)
    - Vincent, Lovina F., 1941 (Box 228:4958)
    - Vincent, Mary Delia, 1950 (Box 228:4959)
    - Vincent, Mary H., 1941 (Box 228:4960)
    - Vincent, Mary K., 1946 (Box 228:4961)
    - Vincent, Norman E., 1940 (Box 228:4962)
    - Vincent, Ovila W., 1940 (Box 228:4963)
    - Vincent, Phoebe R., 1943 (Box 228:4964)
    - Vincent, Robert, 1957 (Box 228:4965)
    - Vincent, Victor, 1939 (Box 228:4966)
    - Violette, Malvena M. D., 1937 (Box 228:4967)
    - Vitiaz, Victor, 1942 (Box 228:4968)
    - Volpe, Ernestine B., 1955 (Box 228:4969)
    - Vosper, Leo J., 1939 (Box 228:4970)
    - Vosper, Rose Donis, 1941 (Box 228:4971)
    - Vukas, Samuel, 1940 (Box 228:4972)
    - Vriga, Dumica, 1955 (Box 228:4973)
    - Waddington, James, 1956 (Box 228:4974)
    - Wade, Loretta H., 1937 (Box 228:4975)
    - Wajda, Frank, 1953 (Box 228:4976)
    - Wakely, Esther B., 1940 (Box 228:4977)
    - Walas, Anotni, 1948 (Box 228:4978)
    - Walden, Charlotte, 1955 (Box 228:4979)
    - Walden, Winthrop, Jr., 1955 (Box 228:4980)
    - Ward, Edna I., 1955 (Box 228:4981)
    - Ward, Caroline, 1944 (Box 228:4982)
    - Ward, Clinton, 1944 (Box 228:4983)
    - Ward, Elsie P., 1940 (Box 228:4984)
    - Ward, Richard N., 1939 (Box 228:4985)
    - Wareing, Clifford Sharples, 1941 (Box 228:4986)
    - Warren, Arthur, 1954 (Box 228:4987)
    - Warren, Raymond, 1947 (Box 228:4988)
    - Warren, Ruth C., 1951 (Box 228:4989)
    - Warrender, James Albert, 1947 (Box 228:4990)
    - Waskiewicz, Dorothy, 1942 (Box 228:4991)
    - Waskiewicz, Edward P., 1952 (Box 228:4992)
    - Waskiewicz, Rita E. Gervais, 1953 (Box 228:4993)
    - Watson, Frank, 1951 (Box 228:4994)
    - Watson, Hazel T., 1951 (Box 228:4995)
    - Watson, Thomas A., 1942 (Box 228:4996)
    - Watson, William, 1953 (Box 228:4997)
    - Way, Robert S., 1954 (Box 228:4998)
    - Weaver, Henry F., 1941 (Box 228:4999)
    - Webb, Esther, 1943 (Box 228:5000)
    - Webbley, Frederick, 1950 (Box 228:5001)
    - Webster, Woodrow, 1956 (Box 228:5002)
    - Weeks, Annie M., 1937 (Box 228:5003)
    - Weeks, Charles A., 1945 (Box 228:5004)
    - Weeks, Eugene A., 1944 (Box 228:5005)
    - Weigel, Bertha Gwozdz, 1937 (Box 228:5006)
    - Weigel, Fred M., 1937 (Box 228:5007)
    - Weiss, John A., 1937 (Box 228:5008)
    - Welch, Ernest L., 1946 (Box 228:5009)
    - Weldon, Raymond L., 1946 (Box 228:5010)
    - Welker, Harry, 1942 (Box 228:5011)
    - Wells, Celia A., 1937 (Box 228:5012)
    - Wells, Theodore, 1952 (Box 228:5013)
    - Wennerberg, Signe, 1940 (Box 228:5014)
    - Wernicki, Charles L., 1940 (Box 228:5015)
    - Wernicki, Stanley M., 1941 (Box 228:5016)
    - West, Warren C., 1953 (Box 228:5017)
    - Wezowicz, Joseph, 1944 (Box 228:5018)
    - Whalley, John W., Jr., 1941 (Box 228:5019)
    - Whidden, Harry A., 1945 (Box 228:5020)
    - Whipple, Norman D., 1941 (Box 228:5021)
    - White, Alden E., 1937 (Box 228:5022)
    - White, George, 1956 (Box 228:5023)
    - White, George, 1951 (Box 228:5024)
    - White, Leo, 1951 (Box 228:5025)
    - White, Lorraine, 1957 (Box 228:5026)
    - White, Michael, 1953 (Box 228:5027)
    - White, Richard, 1951 (Box 228:5028)
    - Whiteley, John T., 1950 (Box 228:5029)
    - Whitford, Mary, 1956 (Box 228:5030)
    - Whitman, James E., Jr., 1950 (Box 228:5031)
    - Whitman, Jennie E., 1945 (Box 228:5032)
    - Whitman, Walter, 1943 (Box 228:5033)